Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar
and I work at II Bank.
As you may have seen in the title and thumbnail,
you have showered a lot of love on the previous video.
For that, I sincerely thank you.
Thank you very much for
showing so much love. Many
people have also personally messaged me,
and those who have connected with me before,
who have already
seen me.
When I was selected in II Bank,
I uploaded my first video that I have been
selected in IIC Bank. I have received a lot of
love from
you guys, and many people have also
personally messaged me, and I have
also cleared their doubts here. Today's video is going to be here. It has been
two months since I joined II Bank.
In today's video, I am going to share with you my
personal experience, the experience I had in the past
two
months while working at II Bank.
What have I done and what
happens, how are targets completed,
how is work done
in the banking sector, friends, I have brought all these doubts in
front of you in today's video, friends,
you too must be thinking
that after joining the banking sector,
what all has to be done and brother, is there a target
or is there pressure, what all happens,
brother, it has been two months for me,
now friends, I am going to share my experience in front of you,
before that
friends, I have only one request from you,
if you like the video even a little bit, then
brother, please like the video,
if brother, you are new to this channel, then
friends, please subscribe to the channel here,
brother, such helpful
videos come for you, brother, if brother, you are
looking for a job in the banking sector for yourself
or are searching, then also friends, there is going to be
a good news for you,
I will tell you in the upcoming video, what is going to be the
good news, first of all
you have to like and brother, you have to subscribe to the channel,
now friends,
starting the video, brother, I have been working in IIC Bank for
two months  It has been completed, that is,
two months have been completed for me just two to three days ago,
okay, and brother, my
salary has also come twice, there is no problem,
now friends, let us talk about
my experience,
my personal experience in the banking sector,
brother, is very good, like I get to
see negative comments, I get a
lot of negative comments under the video, I also get a
lot of positive ones, that is one side,
that is the other side, okay, rest of the friends,
my experience here says, brother, you get a
very good reputation here,
when you go to the banking sector, brother,
first of all, you
become a professional, friends, from there you
meet new customers, you meet new clients,
you go out, do meetings,
go to the feed, if brother you have
sales work, then brother, brother, you have to go to the feed as
well, like on my own,
brother, I have sales work as well, there is office work,
brother, I have to go to the feed,
in the feed, I do not have to go to the open market, the
rest I sit in the office  I
make calls etc. and from there the lead
is generated and from there the meeting
etc. is fixed and from there the
sales etc. are done. Friends,
you have asked me many times
in the comment section, what position do you hold? So,
I am a sales executive. Okay,
my work is in the business card and
credit card department.
You have to provide business cards. You have to
deliver pre-approved cards to the customers. You have to explain their
documentation etc. to them and
deliver it to them. Now the
second thing, friends, is that the pressure, the
target is completed.
Otherwise, no, I
told you in the previous video as well that the target and the pressure is there, the
target is achieved. If
you work wholeheartedly and you feel that
you have to work, then you will 100%
complete your target. There is no problem at all. The
pressure is on the one who is
not able to complete the target. It is
not that you have been given a target.  If
you are able to do only five out of 20 cards, then there will be
pressure on you.
If you get a target of 10 or 15
cards, then even if you do 10 of them,
if you get a target of 15 cards, even if you do
10 or 12 of them, but you are unable to do three to four, then there will not be so much
pressure on you. There is no problem.
You will be explained a little and you will be
asked what problem you faced,
why you could not do it. These are the things that happen,
otherwise there will not be any pressure on
you. There are
also comments like, don't do a job in the banking sector. The
job in the banking sector is stable
and it is a permanent job and you
get the highest growth in it.
You can go anywhere, in
any bank, in any sector,
you will not see so much growth. It
is okay in a job, but
you get good opportunities in it, but you are given
increment every year, but you are
promoted every year, if you do good work then
brother  In three to four years, your
salary can be ₹50 to ₹100. There is no problem in this
if you
work diligently. Many people are
also asking me how the interview is conducted and
how one gives the interview. So,
I will make a special video for that.
Friends, you can watch it. In that video, I will
cover everything about how the interview is given and what
questions are
asked. I will make the entire video and
tell you in the comment section. Tell me
whether you want the video or
not. Okay, and brother,
I have told you about my experience. It has been two
months since I started working. My
salary for two months has also been credited to me.
Okay, and brother, my experience is
very good. There is no problem for me.
Work is being done, etc., and the rest of
your staff, etc., they also cooperate with you.
If you compromise with them, then it is
okay. Otherwise, my
experience is quite good. There is no
problem. If you still have
any doubts.  If there is any such thing, then brother, the link is given below.
I hope you liked this video very much. If you liked the
video, then give it a like.
Rest of the brothers, we will meet in the next video. Till then,
take care bye.